DANIEL ALEJANDRO HERNÁNDEZ GÁLVEZ

Frontend Developer

Jalisco, Mexico GMT-6 hernandezgalvezalejandro@gmail.com https://daniel-galvez.elcreadorweb.com/ github.com/DanielHernandezGalvez

I am a developer with about two years of experience in web development. I really like designing and developing the views of applications and websites with technologies such as javascript, react and php. I have contributed to the success of my company by providing web solutions both internally and to clients. I am very passionate about programming, I aspire to become a top-level developer in the future.

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER, WOLF MARKETING 360

SEPTEMBER 2023 - PRESENT

My role is to contact the client to find out their needs and provide a solution with web technologies.

Tech stack: WordPress, PHP, Git, Next.js, React.js, JavaScript, Figma, Typescript, Tailwind, and Bootstrap.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, NÚCLEO DE DIAGNÓSTICO

JANUARY 2023 - JULY 2023

My main responsibility is to develop the views of various company microservices and optimization of the user experience, which has resulted in a significant reduction in execution time.

Tech stack: Next.js, React.js, JavaScript, Git, Figma, Django, CSS, and Bootstrap.

SKILLS

- Programming: Typescript, PHP and Javascript.
- Web Design: HTML, WordPress, CSS,
 Elementor, Tailwind, Bootstrap and SCSS.
- Productivity tools: Git, Notion y Monday.
- Frameworks: React js, Next js, Django and Express.
- Design: Figma, Illustrator y Photoshop.
- English level: B1 Medium

EDUCATION

FullStack Development Bootcamp - SoyHenry

Frontend Development Career with React - CoderHouse

Bachelor's Degree in Public Relations and Communication - UdG

Computer Science - CECATI 56

2022

2017-2021

2019-2020